

Matteo Luceri

Ravenna (RA), Italy

+39 340 73 67 218

matteoluceri@msn.com

Link

LinkedIn



GitHub

Languages

Italian - Native

English - B2.2

Hard Skills

JS, React, Next, Typescript

HCI - UX Test

Clifton Strengths —

Intellection

Introspective and appreciate intellectual discussion

📃 Learner

Desire to learn and want to continuously improve.

Input

Need to collect and archive: information, ideas, artifacts or even relationship.

! Restorative

Adept at dealing with problems. Good at figuring out what is wrong and resolving it.

Connectedness

Faith in the links among all things:

there are few coincidences, almost every event has meaning.

About Me

In July 2020 I graduated in Computer Science. In November, I started my career as Android App developer. After that I approached FE development, developing multi-platform app using React Native.

I fell in love with JavaScript and its potential by specializing in technologies such as React, Next, Typescript.

At the moment I work as consultant FE dev and my ambition is to continue the exploration of JS potential by embracing the idea of "JavaScript everywhere".

Besides developing, my other great passions are music and reading. I've been playing guitar for 12 years and I write songs that I like to share online. I am very curious (I like to see myself as a T-shaped person) and this leads me to read a lot. Too many things to learn! (... and so little time)

Working Experience

November Front-End Developer Consultant

Innoteam s.r.l. FE consultant at the moment for a big Milan company. I'm supporting

FE team to maintain, refactor and to re-brand the web-site after

company acquisition.

November **App/Front-End Developer**

I-Tel s.r.l.

2020 -November 2021

2021 -

present

Development of native app in Android. Development of cross-

platform mobile applications in React Native.

March – June

Undergraduate internship Università Degli Studi Di Bari "Aldo Moro" I did my internship in the math department where I did a research 2020

and development about "Compressive Sensing(CS) in Smart Grid

(SG) monitoring systems".

2015 – 2017 Woodworking and Renovation

2011 - 2015 Waiter

Education

BSc: Computer Science And 2017 - 2020

Università Degli Studi Di Bari "Aldo Moro" **Digital Communication**

Focus: Theoretical foundations of programming, languages and algorithmics, computability and complexity, methods for multimedia

applications aimed at a wide range of application domains.

2009 – 2013 **High School Diploma** I.I.S.S. "Luigi Einaudi" - Manduria

Focus: Programming, Law and Economics Programmer-Accountant Diploma

Projects

BSc Thesis An dynamic solution for SmartGrids monitoring by combining con-

> cepts related to Compressive Sensing (CS) and Sparse Recovery (SR). I implemented a SG model in MATLAB, with the aim to show and finally to compare some applications of CS - SR algorithmic

techniques.

The web app allows expression recognition in live (via web cam) and MoodIndigo

offline, loading a local video and obtaining a .csv output. In this project I held the role of team leader, and I performed a fullstack

work using Laravel framework.

For more Please visit my portfolio.

Programming - Software & Languages

Storybook JavaScript **Typescript** React/React-Native Chromatic Redux / RTK Webpack NodeJs Cypress Jest Styled Components Mac/Linux/Windows Git Android **MATLAB** Vim LAT_FX- Beamer Java